[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important bone-building mineral do the cartilage of bats finger bones lack, which makes them very flexible?", "correct_answer": "Calcium", "incorrect_answers": ["Potassium", "Magnesium", "Iron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This drink contains caffeine.", "correct_answer": "Coffee", "incorrect_answers": ["Mineral water", "Orange juice", "Beer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Greek it is Sayapo, in Lakota it is Techihhila, in Lithuanian it is Tave myliu, in Albanian it is te dua. What is it in English?", "correct_answer": "I love you", "incorrect_answers": ["I need help", "Hello", "Good morning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie shown in the White House?", "correct_answer": "Cabira", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sheik", "Wings", "The Birth of a Nation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the national motto of the Federative Republic of Brazil, also featured in the national flag of the country?", "correct_answer": "Order and Progress", "incorrect_answers": ["Faith and Honesty", "Freedom Above All", "Unity and Strength"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2008, how many nations had aircraft carriers either sea worthy or under construction?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["14", "2", "20"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Miracle, coach Herb Brooks had to cut a player just before the start of the Olympics. Who was the unfortunate player?", "correct_answer": "Ralph Cox", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Johnson", "Dave Christian", "Steve Janaszak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For the 1994s massive movie hit The Lion King Rowan Atkinson gave his voice to this bird character.", "correct_answer": "Zazu", "incorrect_answers": ["Pumbaa", "Rafiki", "Timon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the third-tallest waterfall on the planet, Ramnefjellsfossen, located?", "correct_answer": "Norway", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Switzerland", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedian stars in Who Framed Roger Rabbit (a 1988 motion picture).", "correct_answer": "Bob Hoskins", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Varney", "Jim Carrey", "Danny DeVito"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Napoleon Dynamite, Pedro has a bicycle about which Napoleon asks if he ever takes it off any sweet jumps? What kind of bicycle is it?", "correct_answer": "Sledgehammer", "incorrect_answers": ["Shwinn", "Huffy", "Mongoose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Consuming alcohol raises your body temperature.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]